我哋已經非常習慣有互聯網
我哋不停分享一啲關於我哋自己同埋個人生活嘅資訊
我哋食嘅嘢，我哋見到嘅人
我哋去嘅地方，我哋讀緊嘅書
等我解釋長細啲啦
就喺呢個時候，
如果有人上網嘗試追蹤你
佢哋可以見到你真正嘅身份，
準確嘅位置同你部電腦嘅作業系統
你上過嘅網站，你所用嘅瀏覽器
同埋好多好多關於你同埋你生活嘅資料
你本身都唔發覺同咗啲三唔識七嘅人分享
佢哋可以好容易地利用呢啲資料
不過如果你用Tor嘅話
Tor保護您嘅個人私隱同埋您嘅身份
Tor secures your connection
with three layers of encryption
and passes it through three voluntarily
operated servers around the world,
which enables us to communicate
anonymously over the Internet.
Tor also protects our data
against corporate or government targeted
and mass surveillance.
Perhaps you live in a repressive country
which tries to control and surveil the Internet.
Or perhaps you don't want big corporations
taking advantage of your personal information.
Tor makes all of its users
to look the same
which confuses the observer
and makes you anonymous.
So, the more people use the Tor network,
the stronger it gets
as it's easier to hide in a crowd
of people who look exactly the same.
You can bypass the censorship
without being worried about
the censor knowing what you do
on the Internet.
The ads won't follow you
everywhere for months,
starting when you first
clicked on a product.
By using Tor, the sites you visit
won't even know who you are,
from what part of the world
you're visiting them,
unless you login and tell them so.
By downloading and using Tor,
you can protect the people
who need anonymity,
like activists, journalists and bloggers.
Download and use Tor! Or run a relay!